

CONTACT ME

Morocco, Tanger Branes 2

zakariaelharrak07@gmail.com

☐ https://github.com/zakariaelharrak

in @zakaria-elharrak

+212 691137409

EDUCATION

Course studied

Baccalauréat (a.bien)

2021 - 2022

Course studied

Front End Libraries & Responsive Web Design (freeCodeCamp)

2020 - 2021

Course studied Front End Development (maharatech)

2020 - 2021

LANGUAGES

Arabic

Anglais

French

SKILLSET

JavaScript , HTML,CSS/Sass, MySQL, Python, R, PHP

Git, Gulp, Webpack, Netlify, Heroku, Prismic, Contentful, Craft, Wordpress, Docker, Firebase

Sketch, InVision, InDesign

Zakariae ElHarrak

WordPress/PHP Developer

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Designer & Devloper

2021 - 2022

Freelancing

Communicate and collaborate with multidisciplinary teams of engineers, designers, producers, customers and stakeholders on a daily basis

focus more on modern professional projects, learn more about new technologies.

Full stuck devloper

2020 - 2021

Startup Happysoulmagazine

Worked with a team of two designers and manager to create clean and professional websites of all types

(e-commerce, Portfolios...)

Built and helped create more than 6 incredible new startups using Wordpress

Frent-End devloper

2019 - 2020

Startup Mrsolutions

built and code high quality projects for daily customers.

Develop and maintain code for internal websites and clients primarily using Wordpress ,HTML, CSS,

Sass, Javascript and jQuery...

Sites tested in various browsers and devices to ensure browser-to-mobile compatibility reactivity

Brands I used Wordpress for building Them.

chlaytan, sscalifornia, graphizoom, dentalyousr, tangergaming, infinimarketing, mrsolutions, hichamylog, happysoulmagazine

ABOUT ME

I design and code beautifully simple things, and I love what I do. I'm a Full-stuck Developer which made a lot of sites,apps... for startups and companys using Html,Css,Php,Wordpress...,I am located in Morocco Tangier . I have a serious passion for UI, dynamic user experiences, Ai Developments, Future of web developments (Web 3).

Well-organised person, problem solver, independent employee with high attention to detail. Fan of Mountain Biking, outdoor activities, TV series and Arabic literature. A family person,

Interested in the entire frontend and back-end spectrum and working on ambitious projects with positive people.